#### **Nationality**

Colombian

#### **Date of Birth**

14/04/1992

#### **Address**

Calle 18a #50-97 blo 3 apt 202 191507 Cali, Colombia

#### Contact

+57 316 707 33 25 zuluaaristi@gmail.com

#### Github

github.com/dafer154

#### LinkedIn

www.linkedin.com/in/davidfza25/

#### Personal page

dafer154.github.io/portafolio

#### **Skills**

#### **Technical**

Advance: HTML, CSS

**Good:** Javascript, Typescript, Django, Python, React, Angular

Basic: Java, C++

#### Languages

Spanish: Native English: A2

## **Personal Projects**

StarMovieList - API TMDB dafer154.github.io/starmovielist

**Technologies:** Angular 6, TypeScript, CSS3, Bootstrap 4, Web responsive

Personal Portfolio dafer154.github.io/portafolio

**Technologies:** Angular 6, Typescript, CSS3, Bootstrap 4

#### **Talks**

Consuming an API using Angular Meetup Pioneras Dev (Jul 2019) github.com/dafer154/appDevHac

Async web with Django Channels Meetup Python-Cali (Dec 2018) https://bit.lv/2zm83Tr

# **David Fernando Zuluaga**

Software Engineer with 2 years of experience in software development using in Front-End Technologies such as HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Angular, TypeScript and React, and Backend technologies such as Python, Django rest framework, Django channels, and PostgreSQL. I also have experience in Database design and Service Oriented Architectures. Other skills include teamwork and autonomous learning

## **Education and Training**

2013 - 2017

#### **Bachelor of Systems Engineering**

"Herramienta web para visualización de material educativo en el aula de clase y evaluación continua" (Educational Web Application, Django, Django-channels, Django-tenant, Bootstrap)

JavaScript, PostgreSQL, Agile Development, Software Testing

The application allows teachers to evaluate students' performance in real time Universidad del Valle, Cali, Colombia

2009 - 2013

#### **Technology in Information Systems**

Training Program in Systems Engineering (7 semesters) Universidad del Valle, Cali, Colombia

## **Experience**

May 2019 - Dec2019

## **Frontend Developer Project:** Ortho 360

Developer of "ORTHO 360", the employed technologies are: C#, .NET, for the backend and Angular7, and Javascript for the front-end including Flexbox and CSS3 for responsive behaviour

Squareball studios, Cali, Colombia

Nov 2017 - Jul 2018

#### **Fullstack Developer**

Project: Gimnasio de habilidades

Developer of the "Gimnasio de habilidades", a gamified system that allows students to reinforce knowledge of quantitative reasoning and critical reading. The employed technologies are: Python, Django rest framework for the API management PostgrestSQL, Postman. The Frontend included React, Javascript and Flexbox and

CSS3 for responsive design CIER Sur, Universidad del valle, Cali, Colombia

Dec 2015 - May 2016

#### **Development analyst**

**Project:** Unificacion PSP-OCCIRED

Member of the development team of the business banking unit, in charge of the PSP OCCIRED project, managing services with SOAP UI, and an ORACLE database Control of logs of data through ESB(Bus enterprise service)

Banco de occidente, Cali, Colombia

Jun 2015 - Dec 2015

#### **Trainee**

**Project:** Sistema de cartera FACTORING

Software tester, evaluating the quality of the product, performing the test summary, identifying the scope of the test, design and performing of test

Analysis of test results, conducting time estimation on assigned projects, elaboration and evaluation of a test plan and a test strategy for the project, recording and tracking of identified issues

Banco de occidente, Cali, Colombia